<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<generalHealth last-updated="2016-10-03" page-url="https://medlineplus.gov/definitions/generalhealthdefinitions.html" title="General Health">
		<term-group reference="NIH MedlinePlus" reference-url="https://medlineplus.gov/">
			<term>Basal Body Tempature</term>
			<definition>Basal body temperature is your temperature at rest when you wake up in the morning. This temperature rises slightly around the time of ovulation. Keeping track of this temperature and other changes such as cervical mucus may help you figure out when you are ovulating. Take your temperature before you get out of bed every morning. Since the change during ovulation is only about 1/2 degree F (1/3 degree C), you should use a sensitive thermometer such as a basal body thermometer.</definition>
			<icon>bodyTemperature.png</icon>
		</term-group>

		<term-group reference="National Institute on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism" reference-url="http://pubs.niaaa.nih.gov/publications/AlcoholOverdoseFactsheet/Overdosefact.htm">
			<term>Blood Alcohol Content</term>
			<definition>Blood alcohol content, or blood alcohol concentration (BAC), is the amount of alcohol in a given volume of blood. For medical and legal purposes, BAC is expressed as grams of alcohol in a 100 milliliter sample of blood.</definition>
			<icon>bloodAlcohool.png</icon>
		</term-group>

		<term-group reference="National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute" reference-url="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/">
			<term>Blood Pressure</term>
			<definition>Blood pressure is the force of blood pushing against the walls of the arteries as your heart pumps blood. It includes two measurements. "Systolic" is your blood pressure when your heart beats while pumping blood. "Diastolic" is your blood pressure when the heart is at rest between beats. You usually see blood pressure numbers written with the systolic number above or before the diastolic number. For example, you might see 120/80.</definition>
			<icon>bloodPressure.png</icon>
		</term-group>

		<term-group reference="NIH MedlinePlus" reference-url="https://medlineplus.gov/rhincompatibility.html">
			<term>Blood Type</term>
			<definition>There are four major blood types: A, B, O, and AB. The types are based on substances on the surface of the blood cells. Besides blood types, there is the Rh factor. It is a protein on red blood cells. Most people are Rh-positive; they have Rh factor. Rh-negative people don't have it. Rh factor is inherited though genes.</definition>
			<icon>bloodType.png</icon>
		</term-group>

		<term-group reference="National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute" reference-url="http://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/public/heart/obesity/lose_wt/risk.htm">
			<term>Body Mass Index</term>
			<definition>Body Mass Index (BMI) is an estimate of your body fat. It is calculated from your height and weight. It can tell you whether you are underweight, normal, overweight, or obese. It can help you gauge your risk for diseases that can occur with more body fat.</definition>
			<icon>bmi.png</icon>
		</term-group>

		<term-group reference="NIH MedlinePlus" reference-url="https://medlineplus.gov/">
			<term>Body Temperature</term>
			<definition>Body temperature is a measure of your body’s level of heat.</definition>
			<icon>bodyTemperature.png</icon>
		</term-group>

		<term-group reference="NIH MedlinePlus" reference-url="https://medlineplus.gov/">
			<term>Cervical Mucus</term>
			<definition>Cervical mucus comes from the cervix. It collects in the vagina. Tracking the changes in your mucus during your cycle, along with changes in your basal body temperature, may help you figure out when you are ovulating.</definition>
			<icon>cervicalMucus.png</icon>
		</term-group>

		<term-group reference="NIH MedlinePlus" reference-url="https://medlineplus.gov/">
			<term>Galvanic Skin Response</term>
			<definition>Galvanic skin response is a change in electrical resistance of the skin. It can occur in response to emotional arousal or other conditions.</definition>
			<icon>galvanicSkinResponse.png</icon>
		</term-group>

		<term-group reference="National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute" reference-url="http://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/health-topics/topics/hhw/contraction.html">
			<term>Heart Rate</term>
			<definition>Heart rate, or pulse, is how many times your heart beats in a period of time — usually a minute. The usual pulse for an adult is 60 to 100 beats per minute after resting for at least 10 minutes.</definition>
			<icon>heartRate.png</icon>
		</term-group>
	</generalHealth>
